this place is unreal  it feels like i'm really in north korea  can if you are white pickle queen my  name is lishin khan of the khan dynasty  i'll be your waiter for this evening can  i show you to your seats  you  look i'm not racist but can we have a  way to who was actually born in this  country  oh come on don't even bother acting sad  nobody here is going to feel bad for you  you know what never mind we'll just go  find our seats ourselves come on kids  manic stop eating the crayons i want a  hamburger they don't have hamburgers  here it's the chinese buffet not  mcdonald  mommy i want pizza  sonia sweetie they only have chinese  food here chinese people don't eat pizza  chinese people suck i hate chinese  people then sonia don't be racist  outside of the house i'm hungry when is  the food going to get here this is a  buffet which means you go up and grab it  yourself how do i know what to grab  mommy you can grab anything you want  [ __ ] i mean son  really anything yes  anything holy [ __ ] this is the best day  of my life  yo gunky poops help me out of this chair  i've been having trouble standing up  lately  jesus he was stood in upon china before  a welcome elendi learned something  called what  did you know the philippines has telugu  of consent on earth  atollido  what does that have to do with china  so like what do we get i've never seen  any of this food before  what's that  i think that's raw fish  that is disgusting  what are those things over there  they look kind of like burritos from  taco bell  hey look at that white stuff it looks  like little beans  whoa you're right it does look like  beans what do you think it is  you know maybe this food isn't all that  strange after all  it's different but maybe different is a  good thing i think we can do this sibs  hey kid let go do you know who the [ __ ]  i am i'm bart levi montclair of  dresden's [ __ ] shut up fat white boy  you have no power here in my family's  restaurant i'm the 13th son of the head  chef and the next in line is head of the  chang dynasty if you do not give me the  sushi i will bring dishonor to you rip  off your head shove it up my butt and  make you disappear son what the hell do  you think you are doing i told you you  are only allowed once a week are you  trying to bring the sauna to your family  i will punish you severely if you do not  get your ass back to the rice fields in  the next seconds  [Music]  [Music]  see you again i will send other family  ninjas after you  father where are you going don't walk  away from my grandma warrior that  if you are so willing to die to prove  your loyalty then you can do it yourself  more  more  more  [Music]  greeting chosen family are you enjoying  your meal our egg-based noodles were  made by chinese people who spent 6 years  of their lives learning how to toss  noodles and [ __ ]  oh yes before i forget here you go don't  worry about leaving 84 extra money we  chinese people don't do that  ah wait what is this  that is the bill for your new please pay  before you leave  oh the bill well all right let's see  what the damage is i suppose  this is way too much there's no way i  have that kind of money  eight hundred dollars  actually it's only eight dollars  eight dollars who do you think i am  there's no way i have that kind of money  what kind of scam do you think you're  pulling here  calm down  [Music]  what about 98 of what you can find in  walmart  what was that  why don't you check the tag on your  shirt that is if you got the smelly ball  sack to be a man to prove that you are  right  okay you  don't do it uncle chuck don't you do it  you know what's gonna happen if that tax  is made in china you're gonna look like  a [ __ ] a [ __ ] [ __ ] you know it's  gonna be there me and my people made  that [ __ ] uncle chuck don't embarrass  yourself  mom get out try to make a [ __ ] video  [Music]  luke you don't have anything to worry  about lucky for you we're having a  weekend discount as long as you haven't  passed the threshold of 50 plates your  meal gets to be half of the usual price  half off for under 50 plates that's  great  there's no way we broke past that right  kids  did you say something mommy  what's the matter son yo soul best  milling  araguano tina building atlearos  my my daddy did karate chop on my balls  because i got deep breaths in mass class  today he also said i can't come home  until i bring back go nuts with my  family  hey kid  look at me [ __ ]  look  sucky your world  look i understand your situation but to  put it bluntly i don't care  if you can't pay up i'm going to drop a  steaming dookie right on your face and  then call the police  you can't there has to be something we  can do  we'll help cook wash dishes  i'll do it  anything to protect my family  believe if it is your decision what you  must do is defeat our head  the monk you created  for today in single combat  [Music]  do you accept these rules  how about no  how about yes  [Music]  get off the floor right now i'm gonna  make you suck my huge balls before  nurturing you  i can't watch this  i can  [Music]  [Applause]  bart levy can you kick jackie chan's ass  [ __ ] i don't even know who jackie chan  is  bart levy if i studied karate would you  watch some of my techniques  not unless one of those moves can get  the dried crustacean stain off the  bottom of my toilet seat  that's it i know just the right move to  take care of you  you did it bro you saved us now we can  get 30  off our meal  that's our bro  what do you say we celebrate this with  even more beans  [Music]  this episode of sonic underground is  dedicated to all those who lost their  lives in the highland park 4th of july  parade massacre for those who are still  alive remember to love each other stay  safe and maybe even have a little fun on  the side and remember if you ever find  yourself in a mass shooting make sure to  run indoors where the shooter can't get  you don't run down the street where  you'll be an easy target  and also remember if you ever lose a  family member or a friend to a mass  shooting don't forget it could always be  worse like when sonic underground was  cancelled after only one season or like  when sonic underground came back on  disney xd only to be cancelled a second  time  [Music]  [Music]  every step that i take is  [Music]  [Music]  is holding too tightly i'm afraid to  lose control cause everything that you  thought i would be  has fallen apart right in front of you  tony  [Music]  is  [Music]  [Music]  [Music]  oh  [Music]  tv